So let's remember the code we had at the end of unit 2 for crawling the web.
先来回忆一下第二单位结尾学到的抓取网页代码
So we used 2 variables. We initialized "tocrawl" to the seed, a list containing just the seed,
我们用了两个变量 将 tocrawl 初始化为只包含种子页面的列表
and we're going to use "tocrawl" to keep track of the pages to crawl.
再用 tocrawl 来跟踪需要抓取的页面
We initialized "crawled" to the empty list, and we're keeping track of the pages we found using "crawled."
我们将 crawled 初始化为空列表  并用 crawled 来跟踪已被抓取的网页
Then we had a loop that would continue as long as there were pages left to crawl.
这样 只要仍有页面需要抓取 循环就会继续
We'd pop the last page off the "tocrawl" list.
我们可弹出 (pop 操作) tocrawl 列表的最后一个网页
If it's not already crawled, then we'll union into "tocrawl" all the links that we can find on that page,
如尚未抓取 则将该页面找到的所有链接合并放入到 tocrawl 中
and then we'll add that page to the list of pages we've already crawled.
之后 再将该页面添加进抓取完毕的网页列表
So now we want to figure out how to change this so instead of just finding all the URLs,
现在我们要了解 如何进行改变才可以不仅查找所有 URL
we're building up our index.
还要构建我们自己的索引
We're looking at the actual content of the pages, and we're adding it to our index.
我们浏览页面的实际内容 并添加进索引
So the first change to make, we're updating the index, and we're going to change the return result.
因此 第一个变动就是更新索引 并改变返回结果
So instead of returning "crawled" what we want to return at the end is the index.
所以我们最后不是返回 crawled 而是返回 index
`If we wanted to keep track of all the URLs crawled, we could still return "crawled" and return both "crawled" and "index,"
如希望对所有搜索过 URL 进行跟踪 则仍可返回 crawled 并在最后返回 crawled 和 index 两个结果
but let's keep things simple and just return "index."
但为了简单起见 这里仅仅返回 index
That's what we really want for being able to respond to search queries.
要对搜索查询作出响应 这是切实需要的
So now we have one other change to make, and this is the important one.
现在要做另一个很重要的变动
We need to find a way to update the index to reflect all the words that are found on the page that we've just crawled.
我们要设法更新索引 来映射在抓取过的页面上找到的所有词
I'm going to make one change before we do that.
这之前 我要先做个改动
Since both "getalllinks" and what we need to do to add the words to the index depend on the page,
因为 get_all_links 和我们将词添加进索引的工作都依赖网页
let's introduce a new variable and store the content of the page in that variable.
所以 要引入一个新变量 并将网页内容存储在于该变量
This will save us from having to call "get_page" twice. "Get_page" is fairly expensive.
这样就不用两次调用 get_page 了 这个过程其实挺昂贵的
It requires a web request to get the content of the page.
它需要一个网络请求来获得网页内容
It makes a lot more sense to store that in a new variable, and that will simplify this code.
将之存储在新变量中更加合理 并可简化代码
So now we just need to pass in content.
现在 我们只需传入 content
So we have one missing statement,
这里缺少一个语句
and I'll leave it to you to see if you can figure out statement we need there to finish the web crawler.
我希望大家能够找出这个语句 来完成网络爬虫
When it's done, the result of "crawl-web," what we return as "index"
完成后 crawl_web 的结果 即返回的 index
should be an index of all the content we find starting from the seed.
应当就是从种子页面找到的所有内容的索引